ecobabymamadrama.com 2011-12-16

# Eco Baby Mama Drama: PR/Media/Privacy Policy

Thank you for your interest in working with me and being featured on my blog!  I am always open to trying any Eco-friendly products including but not limited to: cloth diapers, cloth wipes, cloth diapering accessories, mama cloth, reusable breast pads (if I am breastfeeding),  green cleaning products and other household items such as reusable bags and energy efficiency products.  If you have a product you would like to discuss with me to see if my blog is a fit for your company please contact me!  

If you are interested in me doing a product **_review only_** , I request that you send me a full sized product for the review and allow for a 3 to 8 weeks turnaround time from when I receive the product until the review posting on my blog (unless otherwise agreed upon).  I reserve the right to refuse a review post if you send an item that is different than what was agreed upon.  Sample sizes are NOT allowed and if sent will not be reviewed, review items are requested to be at least $25 value.  I am not responsible for shipping costs and any items sent COD will be refused.  

My reviews consist of my honest thoughts and opinions of product(s) along with action shots of the item(s) sent being used.  I will also include information on your/your company and links and pictures back to you.  Please be aware that any negative thought or areas of improvement will be posted with my positive thoughts.  Not every product is 100% positive for everyone, however if I have a negative experience or suggestion for improvement I will contact you for feedback.  

If you would like to do a ** _review and giveaway_** , the review process as stated above is the same, the giveaway can be for either the same item(s) I reviewed, 1 or more item(s) if I reviewed several, store credit (gift certificate/card) to your business, or an item similar to one that I featured on my blog.  Please make sure you are specific on the giveaway item and the requirements for winnings.   Please specify if the giveaway is open worldwide, USA only or USA and Canada.  Unless otherwise agreed upon it is the sponsors (not EBMD blog) responsibility to ship the prize to the winner.  My winners are selected via Random.org and emailed by me and have 48 hours to respond (unless otherwise stated).  If no response is received another winner will be chosen via Random.org and notified.  When a winner responds to me with their shipping information I will them forward the information on to you.    

The Guinea Pigs:  

Bri:  I am a stay at home mom with a background most recently in technology procurement.  I am a multi tasking busy mom and have a very wide range of interests.    

DJ: My husband is in the IT field and is well versed in several aspects of technology.  

T-Bone:  my oldest is 13 years old and is also interested in technology, he loves music, outdoors, and has a blog of his own!  

Tates: the youngest (currently) of the bunch is 20 months old and learning new things everyday.  He is a big boy for his age.  

**Please check with me prior to sending sized items or gender specific items**  

**_Privacy Policy_**  
**_  
_**  
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Eco Baby Mama Drama Blog collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the <http://www.ecobabymamadrama.com/> website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Eco Baby Mama Drama Blog .

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Eco Baby Mama Drama Blog collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature_  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Changes to this privacy policy

Eco Baby Mama Drama Blog has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
<http://www.ecobabymamadrama.com/>  
http://www.ecobabymamadrama.com/ ecobabymamadrama at gmail dot com  
ecobabymamadrama@gmail.com

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

This document was last updated on October 03, 2011
